Later this week, Aaliyah is planning to lead a kick-off meeting with the transformation team.
She wants to make sure that she’s clear about her priorities, and that she uses the time efficiently.
She’s thinking through the agenda and is feeling stuck.
She calls David Fu, who is a MODA board member and an advisor to the transformation team.
“David, hi — do you have a minute to chat?”
“Hey, Aaliyah. Sure. How can I help?”
“I’m trying to wrap my head around this team kick-off. There’s so much ground I want to cover, and I know I only have 30 minutes.”
“Yeah, we’ve all been there before. What do you have so far?”
“I’d like to get to five things:
align on the scope of the transformation, identify the key deliverables, set deadlines,
align on how we’ll work together — and, of course, get to know everyone.”
“Oof, I really don’t want to rush this.”
“David, what do I do?”
“That sounds like a lot, Aaliyah. What are your top priorities?”
“Hmm — my top priorities are making sure we start off on the right foot and get to know each other better.
I also think the team is eager to hear how we’ll be working together over the next few months.
And if we have time, I want to touch on the priority deliverables we have coming up soon.”
“That sounds reasonable.
It would be really helpful to think about what you want to get out of this meeting — and also what your team might need.”
“Maybe try to gauge their needs, huh? Good point.
Let me see if I can go catch someone from the team now and see what’s on their mind.”
“Hey Noah, working late?”
“Story of my life. I’m just quickly finishing up.
My partner’s mum is visiting tonight for dinner.”
“In that case, could I borrow five minutes of your time?”
“Sure, what’s up?”
“I’m a bit stuck. I’m thinking about tomorrow and trying to define the purpose of our transformation team kick-off.
Can I walk you through the agenda and see if there’s anything else you or the team would like to add?”